classifieds1000.com 2014-02-16

# Privacy Policy for GLR Sales LLC

**Privacy Policy**

The policies here relate to all websites operated by GLR Sales, LLC.

* * *

Our websites offer a number of social networking / publishing features which may include:

  * user registration and profile
  * hashtags
  * direct messaging between users   

  * bulletin board / message forum
  * photo gallery
  * member profiles
  * classified ads
  * and/or products / services for sale. 

* * *

**Overview**

This is a social networking website. With very few exceptions, ie: where you enter your email address to register or login, **all of the information you enter on our site will be published on this site.** This means that the search engines bots will read and index what you publish. Additionally people and other bots from anywhere in the world may also read and/or copy whatever you publish. We have no control over what people or bots access the page and/or what the people or bots do with the information.

For that reason it is not advisable to enter your email address except for our website site registration and to login. Additionally it is not advisable to publish phone numbers, addresses, or other personally identifiable information. Even if you delete an entry from our site, we have no control over those who may have copied the information.

* * *

**Commercial Posting**

The purpose of our websites is to be a topical social network. That means the free and open exchange of information, opinions, recommendations, experiences, etc related to the topic of the site. This of course, also includes commercial postings, ie: posting information and links to your products and services.

The key is participation not link dropping (making a post and never returning). However, we are in the processing of limiting the commercial posting to those who also participate socially in an active manner. Some sections require you to "earn points" before you can use them.

In other cases postings and/or links will be deleted if we feel their are unsuitable, ie: a single or multiple short post just to get links to your website. In cases of abuse, ie: repeating commercial postings without any social participation or off-topic commercials posts, your account and access to our network of sites may be disabled.

Those who earn points and have a link published with their post will receive a standard dofollow link. However, if you don't continue to participate over the time link will be changed to a nofollow style link, and later, the link with be replaced with a message that it is an inactive listing.

The cornerstone of our new policy on social participation is for you to build a "expanded profile" (click on your profile) where you can make a comprehensive and interesting page for your business, services, website, etc. You don't need a website to participate, and if you have one you are welcome (and encouraged) to link to it. It is recommended you create an "expanded profile" as the starting point for your participation.

All of your social interaction will be automatically linked to your "profile", leaving you to simply participate socially and build interest in your abilities, skills, interests, experiences and develop friendships that will lead you to be the other members think of when they need your product or service.

Additionally, anyone who engages in commercial posting, through our profiles or otherwise, may be emailed with directly relevant emails. ie: if the moderator deletes a commercial post, if a directory submission is approved, etc.

Please do not enter URLs, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, etc for the titles of your posts, profile name, etc. This may result in the information be replaced with [deleted] and/or the removal of all your accounts. It also means that information is likely to be indexed by the search engines and someone searching for your email address (if you publish it in a post) may find that post.

* * *

**Non-Registered Users**

* * *

> If you participate in any portion of our website we will prompt you for your email address. We do not publish your emails as provided in the specific prompt for it. If you include your email address in your profile, message text or any similar location it will be published along with your message and we have no control over who sees it or how it is used.

We highly recommend you chose to participate as a registered user and do not put contact information directly within your messages. We are not currently accepting posts from unregistered users.

Please note at this time it is required that all users register before they can participate. Users that participated in the past as unregistered uses may register under the same email address they used in the unregistered manner and be able to delete posts. Users that participated with an invalid email address are unable to do so.

* * *

**Registered Users**

* * *

As a registered user you creative a profile(s) and all of your submissions, posts, entries, etc will be published under your profile. When registering you will be asked to provide your email address, name and location. Your email address is not published. Your name and location will be included in your profile and on all your posts. You may wish to use only your first name or a pseudonym. Whatever you provide will be published and it is likely the search engines will index it (often rapidly) and people searching for your name may find your participation on this site.

As a registered user you can send (and receive) short messages to and from other users. You can optionally include your email address. If you provide your email address within our direct message system it will be provided to the other user and we have no control over how they may use it.

* * *

**Information YOU Post (publish)**

* * *

All of the information you submit or post to our site for any of its functions, except for your email address when registering will be published on our website. At the moment it is published, it becomes available to all users of the internet and all search engines to review and make us of in any manner they desire. We have no control over (or knowledge of who) may read, index, and/or use the information.

You should make any submissions or posts with the assumption that it will be indexed by many search engines and any words, text, emails. names, phone numbers, etc that you put within your posts, if used as a search phrase will result in people finding your posts here. You should also assume that others may copy any information you post and republish it online in a form you have no control over.

If you submit a classified ad all of the information except for your email address will be displayed for everyone to see (including any email address you specify in your classified ad). Your email address will only be used to contact you directly regarding your submission (ie: to send your account password and information about approval of your listings).

* * *

**Emails we might send you**

* * *

  * When you register on our site, we will send you an acknowledgement email with your password. You will be sent separately a "welcome" email.  

  * When you request your password be resent to you. 
  * General notifications / subscriptions:

>   * When you register and/or create a profile you are automatically subscribed to " **system messages** ". These are extremely rare and would relate to any significant updates, changes or issues with the site.
>   * When you post an advertisement you status to receive immediately notification when someone sends you a message via our system will be set.
> 

>   * When you post a new message or reply on our forum. You will be added to the email notification list and be sent an email when someone else makes a reply to that message. When posting your message you can uncheck the box and then you will not be added to the email notification list. Additionally, you can select to subscribe or unsubscribe to the notifications for a specific message by using the link at the bottom of the posting form. The notification emails also include an unsubscribe link. 
>   * > Expanded profiles: when you create an expanded profile we may email letting you know your page has been approved, declined or making a comment about in the approval process. Additionally, we email you a weekly status report and/or an individual email to help you with the success of your profile. If you do not wish to receive any such emails you can remove your profile.
> 
>   * > The first time you submit a forum post, note, profile, or other post with a URL included, we may email you information about the most effective self promotional opportunities available to you on our site.
> 
> 

> When you submit a classified ad (ie: real estate, rental, and/or car for sale) we may send you an email when your ad has been approved, rejected, if we have any individual comments or suggestions, and up to once a month with any updates, information, or a request you review your ad for any changes. This refers to classified ads posted within the classified ads section of our website(s), it does not refer to posts made in the forums, blogs, article library, etc. If you do not wish to receive these emails you can delete all your classified ads.

> In the case of a problem or we have a suggestion relative to your submission, posting, account or other issue we may individually email you.

> If you submit an RSS Feed we will send you relevant emails, ie: that your submission was received (or not), when it is approved, and when new posts have been processed and are ready for you to tag them.

> In case you email us with a concern we may email you back.

> You can enable / disable any notifications / subscriptions via the "User Menu / Notifications" selection or you can disable them via the link provided in all emails sent because of a notification or subscription option.

> 

If we receive a spam complaint directly from you, or indirectly, via an email provider (for example, hotmail.com, gmail.com, etc), via an internet carrier, or other third party, regarding any email sent for any of the above reasons, we may disable your account within our system. That means that no emails will be sent to you for password requests, or notifications of comments on posts, or messages sent to you, additionally, you will not be able to login into comment, respond, delete, or in other form access content you have posted under your account. You will not be able to login with alternative services such as Facebook or Google accounts which use the same email address. If you do not wish to receive emails as described above, please turn off notifications and do not use the other sections which directly send an email in response to your actions.

Emails that are returned undeliverable by your email service, for example, because your email address is not recognized by them, your account is over quota, or has expired, may also result in the permanent suspension of any emails being sent to you, including password requests.

If you attempt to participate in any kind of fraudulent activity, or abusive behavior or any activity to attack our servers or network resources any and all information we have or can collect may be shared with anyone we feel is necessary, and/or useful to resolve the problem.

* * *

**Customer Service**

* * *

All of the services provided on our website are free. We do not collect any payments from users. Consequently, all customer service is self-serve and limited.

Before submitting any information, please review the submission form. For example, on forum posts, blog posts, interviews, it is clearly stated that the posts cannot be deleted or edited after submission. Updates can be made by adding comments in the future. However, by logging in under the email that made the post you can delete any forum post or reply.

Submissions to our directory or classifieds ads can be deleted by the same user who placed the advertisement. Please use care when making submissions for clients to ensure your client has the login and password to delete entries in the future if they wish.

All of our customer service is "self-service", ie: you login and delete material posted under your account. In the case that you are unwilling or unable (for example, you hired an SEO company to make posts and they used their login information and not yours), we can provide the following limited customer service: Deletion of a specific post or directory entry. You must provide the exact URL of the post on our site, information to show that it is your post, prepayment of US$50 via Bitcoin or Litecoin (per deletion). Normally within 2 business days of receipt of 6 confirmations of the payment the deletion will be completed.

If you place an order or make use of any website linked to from our website, whether it is an editorial mention with a link, member submission with a link, an advertisement or any other link, you must contact that website directly for any customer service or privacy policy.

If you make a customer service related inquiry on any social networking site, forum, or other publicly accessible website (ie: facebook, twitter,, etc) we may publicly disclose any information we have collected, including but not limited to email addresses, ip addresses, etc in order to respond.

False DMCA requests (ie: requests to delete material you posted yourself, and/or requests with false declarations will be reported to the appropriate authorities).

* * *

**Products and Services listed for Sale**

* * *

Any products listed for sale are from independent websites and you must check directly with them regarding their privacy and other policies. Although we regularly update the product information, you should check directly with the vendor to confirm prices and other product information.

* * *

**Links to Other Websites**

* * *

Our site contains many links to other websites. Some of the links are part of our website and some of the links are included in content posted or submitted by others. If you click either type of link and are taken off our website, ie: **our website url** is no longer shown in your browser address bar, you will need to check with that site for its privacy and other policies.

We have no control or responsibility over content, privacy, or any other aspect of the websites which link to or are linked from our site. All of the user generated content on our site is the responsibility of the user who posted it.

* * *

**Cookies**

* * *

This website does store some information in "cookies" on your computer. It does not store any personally identifiable information in cookies, unless you use a section of our website that requires a login, your login information (email address) may be stored in a cookie for the duration of your being logged in (browser session). If you participate in the forums cookies will be used to help prevent abusive and repeat postings. If you disable cookies, our website may not function properly.

Cookies: If you login on our site, we store a cookie to save your email and encrypted password, and current profile name while you are logged in. We do not store other personally identifiable information in cookies. We store non-personally identifiable information cookies to save various settings and prevent multiple and spam postings.

**Cookies and our advertisers** : Advertisers on our website may set cookies and you should refer directly to an advertisers website for details on their cookies and privacy policy. Their cookies may be set while you surf our site, by virtue of the advertisement being placed in an iframe. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, your need to contact them directly.

"DoubleClick Dart Cookie". Some of our pages may display advertisements provided by Google. Please note the following information with respect to this:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * **Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the[Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)**
